A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Speeches, Series 15 FA383
Rockefeller Archive Center
- April 1-3, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 638)
  New Zealand; Arrival Statement, Toast, Ambassador's Dinner, Remarks to Embassy Staff, Toast, State Luncheon, Toast to Governor-General, Departure Statement; New Zealand, toasts.
- April 5, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 639)
  Washington, DC; Toast to King Gustav of Sweden; toasts.
- April 6, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 640)
  Washington, DC; Dedication of Lyndon B. Johnson Grove, Brief Remarks re: Lyndon B. Johnson; miscellaneous.
- April 7, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 641)
  Reston, VA; Americans for Energy Independence; Energy Independence Authority, energy.
- April 12, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 642)
  Washington, DC, Capitol Hill; Hearings on Energy Independence (Proxmire Committee); energy.
- April 12, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 643)
  Philadelphia, PA, Club of Rome; Remarks on Benjamin Franklin and Dedication of Benjamin Franklin National Memorial; future, economic growth vs. population control, energy, economic freedom.
- April 12, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 644)
  Philadelphia, PA; President Ford Committee Reception; Ford.
- April 13, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 645)
  Washington, DC, State Department; Swearing-In of Christian A. Herter, Jr.; miscellaneous.
- April 14, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 646)
  Des Moines, IA, Veterans Memorial Auditorium; Republican Lincoln Day Dinner, Brief Tribute to Bob Ray, Governor, WHO-TV interview; agriculture, Republican Party.
- NOT USED (Box 17, Folder 647)
- April 15, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 648)
  Atlanta, GA; GOP Fund Raising Reception; Bicentennial re economic, individual and economic freedom, New York re financial problems not only there but throughout the world, Republican Party.
- NOT USED (Box 17, Folder 649)
- April 20, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 650)
  Washington, DC; Kennedy Center, President's Commission on Personnel Interchange Dinner; free enterprise, economic freedom, energy independence, housing, tax laws, revision of regulatory systems, cities, productivity, government.
- April 27, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 651)
  Washington, DC; Statement: NAR Apology to Senate re Scoop Jackson.
- April 28, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 652)
  Washington, DC, Washington Hilton; Annual Neptune Award Dinner, Award to Congressman Charles Mosher, discussed oceanic development re energy, food, minerals, raw materials for economic development for economic growth and job opportunity; economic growth, environment, energy, miscellaneous.
- April 29, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 653)
  Washington, DC, Hyatt Regency; Health Conference, Discussed a National Health Policy; health.
- April 30, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 654)
  Washington, DC, Washington Monument; George Washington Inaugural Ceremony; Bicentennial.
- May 4, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 655)
  San Francisco, CA, Fairmont Hotel; Commonwealth Club Luncheon, America's Role in Foreign Affairs; foreign affairs, national defense, Panama Canal.
- May 5, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 656)
  Los Angeles, CA, Biltmore Hotel; World Affairs Council Luncheon, American Security and the Future of Freedom; foreign affairs, national defense, Panama Canal.
- May 6, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 657)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; Queens County GOP Dinner; politics, Republican Party, New York City.
- May 6, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 658)
  Washington, DC, Pierre Hotel; Beth Moore Reception, United Board of Higher Christian Education in Asia; testimonial, Beth Moore, education.
- May 7, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 659)
  Westport, CT; President Ford Committee Reception; politics, Ford, Republican Party.
- May 9, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 660)
  New York, Lincoln Center; Fund Raising Performance for New York Public Library; arts, New York Public Library.
- May 10, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 661)
  Philadelphia, PA; International Press Institute's General Assembly; foreign affairs, economic growth.
- May 11, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 662)
  New York; Accion Dinner, Presentation of Award to Berent Friele; Panama Canal, Latin American relations.
- May 11, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 663)
  Taped message to Oregon voters for Oregon primary; Ford.
- May 13, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 664)
  Italy; Arrival and Departure Statements; NAR went to view disaster area from earthquake.
- May 13, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 665)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 666)
  Frankfurt and West Berlin, West Germany; Bicentennial Speech, Toasts, Embassy Speech, Arrival and Departure Statements; Bicentennial, Germany, toasts.
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 667)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 668)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 669)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 670)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 671)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 672)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 673)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 674)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 675)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 676)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 677)
- May 14-16, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 678)
- May 19, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 679)
  Yorktown, VA; Bicentennial Ceremony with President Giscard d'Estaing; Bicentennial re Frenchmen helping Americans during Revolution, France.
- May 19, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 680)
  Washington, DC; Toast for Golda Meir; toasts.
- May 20, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 681)
  Cincinnati, OH; President Ford Committee Dinner; Ford, politics, Republican Party.
- May 23, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 682)
  Newport, RI; Touro Synagogue, 50th Anniversary of Synagogue Council of America; religious freedom, Israel and Jews.
- May 26, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 683)
  Washington, DC; National Conference on regulatory Reform; economic growth, regulatory reform, productivity, government.
- May 27, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 684)
  Washington, DC, White House; International Standards Organization; science and technology, economic growth.
- June 2, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 685)
  Colorado Springs, CO; Air Force Academy Commencement; economic freedom, energy, economic growth, national security.
- June 3, 1976 (Empty folder) (Box 19, Folder 0685A)
  Washington, DC, Spanish Embassy; Toast to Juan Carlos; toasts.
- June 4, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 686)
  Ocean City, MD; Maryland State Republican Convention Dinner; Republican Party, politics.
- June 8, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 687)
  Washington, DC, Foxhall (NAR residence); President Ford Committee Reception; Ford, politics, Republican Party.
- June 8, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 688)
  Washington, DC, Kennedy Center; Australian Ballet, interviewed by Australian TV people re his visit to Australia and close ties between United States and Australia; miscellaneous.
- June 9, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 689)
  Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel; National Broadcast Editorial Association Annual Meeting; media, national security.
- June 10, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 690)
  Washington, DC, Fort McNair, Inter-American Defense College; outline notes re Latin American relations.
- June 10, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 691)
  New York; Metropolitan Museum Dinner; New York City; arts.
- June 16, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 692)
  Washington, DC; Dedication of Old Senate Chamber; Bicentennial.
- June 16, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 693)
  Washington, DC; National Housing Conference, tribute to Bob Georgine; miscellaneous.
- June 17, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 694)
  New York, 812 Fifth Avenue (NAR residence); President Ford Committee Reception; Ford, politics, Republican Party.
- June 17, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 695)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; New York State Republican Committee Luncheon; Ford, Republican Party, politics.
- June 17, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 696)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; New York State Republican Committee 28th Annual Dinner; politics, Ford.
- June 18, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 697)
  Greensboro, NC; North Carolina State GOP Convention Dinner; Ford, Republican Party, politics.
- June 21, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 698)
  Newark, NJ; New Jersey State GOP Dinner; Ford, Republican Party, politics.
- June 22, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 699)
  Langley, VA, Central Intelligence Agency; Briefing at Staff Meeting; national security.
- June 22, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 700)
  Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel; American Friends of Hebrew University Luncheon; Israel and Jews.
- June 24, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 701)
  Hauppauge, NY, Colonie Hill Restaurant; Nassau County Republican Committee Annual Dinner, Tribute to Len Hall, Joe Margiotta, and Holly Patterson; Ford, Republican Party, politics.
- June 28, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 702)
  NAR guest editorial in Victor Riezel's Column; no copy here.
- June 29, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 703)
  Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel; Reception for Senator Glenn Beall; miscellaneous.
- June 30, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 704)
  Washington, DC, The Capitol; Atlantic Union, Union of the Free Award Luncheon, Presentation to Paul Findley; miscellaneous.
- July 1, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 705)
  Suitland, MD, Census Bureau; Chartbook Ceremony (STATUS) and anniversary of UNIVAC I; science & technology, computer science.
- July 1, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 706)
  Washington, DC, Italian Embassy; Toast and acceptance of the Award of the Italian Grand Cross; toasts, miscellaneous.
- July 2, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 707)
  Washington, DC; National Archives Documents Ceremony; Bicentennial.
- July 4, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 708)
  Washington, DC, Washington Monument; Happy Birthday USA; Bicentennial.
- July 8, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 709)
  Washington, DC, Capitol Hill; Congressional Luncheon for Queen Elizabeth II; toasts.
- July 9, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 710)
  Washington, DC, Foxhall (NAR residence); Luncheon for Prince Abdallah, Saudi Arabia; toasts.
- July 15, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 711)
  Washington, DC, Smithsonian Institution; Inaugural Ceremony of the Albert Einstein Spacearium. with Chancellor Schmidt (West Germany); science and technology.
- July 19, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 712)
  Claymont, DE, Brandywine Terrace; 1976 Victory Kick-off Dinner; Republican Party, politics.
- July 19, 1976 (Empty folder) (Box 20, Folder 713)
  Wilmington, DE, Hotel DuPont; Press Conference.
- July 28, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 714)
  Washington, DC, Australian Embassy; Toast, Prime Minister Fraser; toasts.
- July 29, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 715)
  Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel; Republican National Hispanic Assembly Reception; ethics, Latin American relations, Republican Party.
- August 2, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 716)
  Seal Harbor, ME, NAR Residence; Maine Republican State Committee Reception; Republican Party.
- August 4, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 717)
  Washington, DC, Anderson House; Luncheon for President Kekkonen of Finland; toasts.
- August 4, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 718)
  Washington, DC, Madison Hotel; dinner and toast for President Kekkonen of Finland; toasts.
- August 9, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 719)
  Kansas City, MO, Municipal Auditorium; Testimony before Republican Platform Committee; foreign affairs, national defense.
- August 16, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 720)
  Kansas City, MO, Kemper Arena; Republican National Convention; Ford, Republican Party.
- August 17, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 721)
  Kansas City, MO, Hotel Meuhlebach; Tennessee State GOP Fund-Raiser, Senator Howard Baker Breakfast; politics, Republican Party.
- August 18, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 722)
  Kansas City, MO, Hotel Meuhlebach; Republican National Committee Finance Committee Luncheon; Republican Party, politics.
- August 19, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 723)
  Kansas City, MO, Kemper Arena; Dole Nominating Speech; Dole, Republican Party.
- August 27, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 724)
  Vail, CO; Press Conference with President Ford, NAR, Bob Dole,John Connally, Rogers C. B. Morton; Campaign '76.
- August 28, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 725)
  Woodstock, VT; Reception for Senator Stafford; miscellaneous.
- September 10, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 726)
  New York, New York Hilton; Roy Wilkins Birthday Reception; African-Americans, testimonials.
- September 16, 1976 (canceled) (Box 20, Folder 727)
  Washington, DC, Fort McNair; Address to National Defense University.
- September 16, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 728)
  Buffalo, NY, Executive Motor Inn; Ford-Dole Campaign Kick-off, Campaign '76.
- September 16, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 729)
  Rochester, NY, Rochester/Monroe County Airport; New York State Ford-Dole Campaign Kick-Off; Campaign '76.
- September 16, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 730)
  Syracuse, NY, Hancock International Airport; New York State Ford-Dole Campaign Kick-Off; Campaign '76.
- September 16, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 731)
  Binghamton, NY, Broome County Airport; New York State Ford-Dole Campaign Kick-Off; Campaign '76.
- September 16, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 732)
  New York, President Ford Headquarters; Press Conference, New York State Ford-Dole Campaign Kick-Off; Campaign '76.
- September 21, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 733)
  Chicago, IL, Conrad Hilton Hotel; Jim Thompson for Governor Fall Campaign Dinner; Campaign '76, Republican Party, politics.
- September 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 734)
  Cleveland, OH; President Ford Committee, Opening Ceremonies of headquarters; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 735)
  Cleveland, OH, Bond Court Hotel; Cuyahoga County Republican Headquarters, Continental Breakfast; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 736)
  Columbus, OH, Fort Hayes Hotel; Columbus Bar Association Luncheon; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 22, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 737)
  Cincinnati, OH, Cincinnati Club; Hamilton County Republican Rally; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 27, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 738)
  Washington, DC, Kennedy Center; Reception Following Israeli Philharmonic Concert; Bicentennial, Israel and Jews.
- September 28, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 739)
  Hasbrook Heights, NJ, Bergen County Sheraton Inn; Brunch Meetings with Candidates; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 28, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 740)
  Dover, NJ, Three Sisters Restaurant; Morris County Republican Party Fund-Raising Luncheon; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 28, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 741)
  Philadelphia, PA, Sheraton Hotel; Press Conference.
- September 28, 1976 (Empty folder) (Box 20, Folder 742)
  Philadelphia, PA, KYW-TV; taping for "The Mike Douglas Show."
- September 28, 1976 (Empty folder) (Box 20, Folder 743)
  Philadelphia, PA, Sheraton Hotel; Live Interview with WCAU-TV.
- September 28, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 744)
  Philadelphia, PA, Sheraton Hotel; Salute to Distinguished Republicans Fund-Raising Dinner; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 29, 1976 (Empty folder) (Box 20, Folder 745)
  Erie, PA, Holiday Inn; Press Conference.
- September 29, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 746)
  Erie, PA, Ciro's Restaurant; Fund-Raising Brunch in Honor of NAR; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 29, 1976 (Empty folder) (Box 20, Folder 747)
  Erie, PA, WICU-TV Studios, TV interview taping.
- September 29, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 748)
  Pittsburgh, PA, Duquesne Club; Industrialists Luncheon; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- September 29, 1976 (Empty folder) (Box 20, Folder 749)
  Pittsburgh, PA, Hilton Hotel; Press Conference.
- September 29, 1976 (Empty folder) (Box 20, Folder 750)
  Pittsburgh, PA, Hilton Hotel; TV taping for KDKA-TV.
- September 29, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 751)
  Pittsburgh, PA, President Ford Committee Headquarters; Candidate Rally; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 5, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 752)
  London, England, United States Embassy; Meeting with US Embassy Staff; Bicentennial.
- October 5, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 753)
  London, England; Two Thousand Years of North American Indian Art; Bicentennial, art.
- October 7, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 754)
  Chicago, IL, Conrad Hilton; Salute to President Ford, Republican National Committee Nationwide Fund-Raiser; Campaign'76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 9, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 755)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; Columbus Citizens Committee Dinner; Italians, Bicentennial.
- October 9, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 756)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; New York County Republican Supporter Dinner; miscellaneous, tribute to Vince Albano, Ford.
- October 9, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 757)
  New York, Americana Hotel; Ukraine-American Congress Annual Dinner; Ford, East Europe.
- October 12, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 758)
  New York, New York Hilton; Salute to President Ford Dinner; Campaign '76, remarks and introduction of Ford.
- October 13, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 759)
  San Francisco, CA; Golden Circle Luncheon; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 13, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 760)
  Portland, OR; Fund-Raising Reception; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 13, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 761)
  Portland, OR; 2nd Fund-Raising Candidate Reception; Campaign '76, Ford.
- October 14, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 762)
  Everett, WA; Candidate Rally; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 14, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 763)
  Everett, WA; Luncheon in Honor of John Nance Garner; Campaign '76, Ford.
- October 14, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 764)
  Seattle, WA; President Ford Committee Meeting; Campaign '76, Ford.
- October 14, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 765)
  Seattle, WA; Heavy Contributors Reception; Campaign '76, Ford.
- October 14, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 766)
  Seattle, WA; Spellman Volunteer Breakfast; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, John Spellman running for governor.
- October 18, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 767)
  Kalamazoo, MI; Brunch; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics, Marvin Esch.
- October 18, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 768)
  Grand Rapids, MI; Hal Sawyer Luncheon; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 18, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 769)
  Saginaw, MI; Fund-Raising Reception; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 18, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 770)
  Detroit, MI; Youth Reception; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 18, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 771)
  Detroit, MI; Fund-Raising Reception; Campaign '76, Ford.
- October 18, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 772)
  Detroit, M, Cobo Hall; Fund-Raising Dinner; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 19, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 773)
  Minneapolis, MN; Candidate Reception; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 19, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 774)
  Minneapolis, MN; Elephant Club Luncheon; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 19, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 775)
  Minneapolis, MN, Normandale Community College; Candidate Rally; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 20, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 776)
  Washington, DC, State Department; Conference: "Stake Of Consumer in Foreign Policy;" economic growth, foreign affairs, Joan Braden, miscellaneous.
- October 21, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 777)
  Wilmington, DE; Reception for Senator Roth; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, miscellaneous re Roth.
- October 21, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 778)
  Washington, DC, National Press Club; Campaign '76, Republican Party, Ford, politics.
- October 26, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 779)
- October 27, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 780)
  Long Island, NY; Senior Citizens Rally; Campaign '76, Ford inflation, senior citizens health.
- October 27, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 781)
  Long Island, NY; Women's Rally-Tea, Hofstra College Meeting; Campaign '76, Ford, economy, inflation.
- October 27, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 782)
  Long Island, NY; Island Park Republican Rally; Campaign '76, Ford, economy, inflation.
- October 27, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 783)
  Long Island, NY; Business, Labor, Education, and Community Leaders Dinner; Campaign '76, Ford, politics.
- October 27, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 784)
  Long Island, NY, Payson-Whitney Tower of North Shore Hospital; health.
- November 7, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 785)
  New York; Eulogy for Gustav Levy; miscellaneous.
- November 12, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 786)
  Williamsburg, VA; Williamsburg Foundation Dinner, 50th Anniversary of Williamsburg Restoration; Rockefeller family, history.
- November 16, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 787)
  Washington, DC, L'Enfant Plaza Hotel; Conference on Future of Productivity; productivity, economic growth, labor, science and technology, government, future.
- November 16, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 788)
  Washington, DC; Republican Eagles Luncheon; Republican Party, politics.
- November 16, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 789)
  Washington, DC, Old Executive Office Building; 10 Outstanding Young American Women; Q&A re Ford, Campaign '76.
- November 16, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 790)
  Washington, DC; Meeting with the Defense Advisory Committee on Women in the Service; national defense, women.
- November 18, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 791)
  Washington, DC; Meeting with National Security Council Staff; miscellaneous, thanked staff.
- November 18, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 792)
  Williamsburg, VA; 22nd Annual Session of the North Atlantic Treaty; foreign affairs, national defense, economy.
- November 21, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 793)
  Pocantico Hills, NY; Exchange of Remarks Among President Ford, NAR, Gary Everhardt at Ceremony Designating John D. Rockefeller Estate a National Historical Landmark; Rockefeller family.
- November 30, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 794)
  New York, Plaza Hotel; China Institute Dinner; China, honoring Brook Astor, miscellaneous.
- December 2, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 795)
  Washington, DC; 100th Anniversary of Pakistan's Founder's Birth; miscellaneous.
- December 7, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 796)
  Washington, DC; Luncheon toast for Prime Minister Giulio Andreotti; miscellaneous.
- December 8, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 797)
  Washington, DC, White House; Presentation of Management Improvement Awards; miscellaneous.
- December 8, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 798)
  Washington, DC, Georgetown University; Graduate Student Forum, federalism.
- December 9, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 799)
  Washington, DC, Fort McNair; National Defense University Address; foreign affairs, national defense, national security, science and technology.
- December 14, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 800)
  Washington, DC, Mount Vernon College; National Capital Area Political Science Association; federalism.
- January 5, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 801)
  Washington, DC; Cabinet Dinner honoring the Fords; Ford.
- Vice Presidential Messages, January 1975 - December 1976 (Box 23, Folder 802)
  NAR letters of congratulation, sympathy, etc.
- Vice Presidential Messages, January 1975 - December 1976 (Box 23, Folder 803)
- Vice Presidential Messages, January 1975 - December 1976 (Box 23, Folder 804)
- Vice Presidential Messages, January 1975 - December 1976 (Box 23, Folder 805)